...He's down but not out.
Jack Irish: Bad Debts is a crime, drama, mystery
film directed by Jeffrey Walker.
Jack Irish is a man getting his life back together again.
A former criminal lawyer whose world imploded, he now spends his days as a part-time investigator, debt
collector, apprentice cabinet maker, punter and sometime lover - the complete man really.
Jack is an expert in finding those who don't want to be found - dead or alive.
He helps out his mates while avoiding the past.
That is until the past finds him.
Jack Irish, played by Guy Pearce.
Linda Hillier, played by Marta Dusseldorp.
Cam Delray, played by Aaron Pedersen.
Harry Strang, played by Roy Billing.
Drew Greer, played by Damien Richardson.
Barry Tregear, played by Shane Jacobson.
Jack Irish is an Australian television drama series first
broadcast on ABC TV on 14 October 2012.
The series stars Guy Pearce as the title character, a former
criminal lawyer turned investigator and debt collector.
Much of the action is set in the Melbourne suburb of Fitzroy.
Adapted from the crime fiction novels by author Peter Temple, the telemovies and series Jack
Irish were developed by Andrew Anastasios, Matt Cameron and Andrew Knight.
They began as three feature-length movies, before being adapted into three
six-episode series, the final one airing from June 2021.
All three movies were directed by Jeffrey Walker, while Kieran
Darcy-Smith serves as lead director on the series.
Bad Debts, the first of the three feature-length movies, was watched by an average of 950,000
Australian viewers, ranking as the sixth most watched programme of the week.
Black Tide, the second movie, was watched by an average of 851,000 Australian
viewers, ranking as the thirteenth most watched programme of the week.
Dead Point, the third and final movie, was watched by an average of 780,000 Australian
viewers, ranking as the eleventh most watched programme of the week.
The first series of six episodes broadcast from 11 February to 17 March 2016.
The second series broadcast from 8 July to 12 August 2018.
The second series was dedicated to the memory of
Peter Temple, who died in March 2018.
The third and final series, Jack Irish: Hell Bent,
premiered on ABC TV and ABC iview on 13 June 2021.
The film explores themes of grenade, client, melbourne,
australia, debt collector, police corruption.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.